AFSCME, District Council 37 Records WAG.265
Tamiment Library / Wagner Archives
Series III: Legal Department Records, 1956-1986, contains legal documents, correspondence, notes, reports, printed material, and newspaper clippings. It provides a snapshot of the Legal Department's multi-faceted work under the leadership of lead counsels Julius Topol and Beverly Gross in the 1970s and early 1980s, from arbitration of grievances to litigation on major social issues of the period. Significant cases represented are James Butler v. DC 37, resulting from Gotbaum and Roberts' dispute with Local 420 President Butler; Daniel Mando, et al. v. Abraham Beame, et al., concerning representation rights for employees hired under the Emergency Employment Act of 1971; and Women in City Government United, et al. v. City of New York, et al., a successful gender discrimination suit challenging the city's use of sex-specific actuarial tables to determine pension contributions and payments. The files also contain material on CSTG's attempt under president Richard Izzo to disaffiliate from DC 37 and on the Deferral Payment Agreement of 1982, under which the city addressed its overdue promise to repay city workers wages deferred during the 1975 fiscal crisis. A significant group of files on pay equity issues from the late 1970s and early 1980s were compiled by Audrey Browne, a Legal Department attorney. They include numerous reports on pay equity issues in New York City and around the country, as well as legal documents relating to AFSCME, et al. v. State of Washington.
Series IV: Communications Department Records, 1963-2004.
Subseries IV:A: Edward Handman Records, 1972-1991, include reports, transcripts, and newspaper clippings compiled by Handman, who served as Director of Public Relations and Publications from 1972 until the early 1990s. Of particular note in this subseries is extensive coverage of two fiscal crises in New York City: the prolonged crisis of the mid-1970s and the shorter but still acute budget crisis of 1991. Handman helped DC 37 craft its response to public perceptions that inflated wages, benefits, and pensions of city workers were responsible for the city's strained budgets.
Subseries IV:B: Bill Schleicher Records, 1992-2004, contains reports, notes, and newspaper clippings compiled by Schleicher in the course of his duties as editor of Public Employee Press(PEP). These materials include annotated minutes of and notes on meetings of delegates, division and department leaders, shop stewards, and the executive board from 2001 to 2004. Of particular note are collected materials--primarily printed materials and reports--on multiple investigations beginning in 1998 by the Manhattan District Attorney of corruption inside DC 37 and its locals. The subseries also contains Schleicher's research material on a variety of local and national issues such as the city budget, contract negotiations, and immigration.
Subseries IV:C: Public Employee Press Research Files, 1963-1993, contains paper records separated from the Public Employee Press photograph files in the DC 37 Photograph Collection (NP #247). These include notes, reports, and copies of documents relating to issues affecting the union as reported by PEP staff, primarily during the 1960s and 1970s. Key issues addressed include safety issues, the union's exposé of poor conditions at the city's public hospitals, the citywide strike of the union's blue collar locals in 1971, the affiliation of municipal and voluntary hospitals, and the contentious representation election of school aides waged by the UFT against DC 37 in 1973.
Series V: General Files, 1944-2000, consists primarily of records kept by DC 37's executive office and printing department from the mid-1950s to the 1970s. This series contains the oldest records in the collection and provides the only documentation of the administrations of executive directors Jerry Wurf, Calogero Taibi, and Victor Gotbaum. Files for nearly every local in the union are present, containing correspondence with executive office staff, salary appeal briefs (predating collective bargaining agreements), minutes, newsletters, printed material such as meeting notices and leaflets, and occasionally constitutions and contracts. Some locals are better represented than others. This series documents key moments in DC 37 history, including the early activism of Locals 149 (Parks) and 299 (Recreation), the 1961 strike of employees at the Bronx Zoo and Coney Island Aquarium, the 1965 welfare workers' strike of Local 371 and SSEU, the 1965 hospital aides representation election, and the 1976 hospital workers' strike. DC 37's Political Action and Legislation Department is also well represented in this series, chronicling the union's growing political strength in the 1970s and 1980s.
Series VI: Restricted Materials, 1967-1997. (Closed for 50 years from date of creation.)
Series VII: Audio Reels--Ken Nash Collection, 1977-1990, contains audio tape reels collected by DC 37's Ken Nash, who was a producer and host of the radio show, "Building Bridges: Your Community & Labor Report." This series is organized into three subseries; the bulk are reels of DC 37's radio show "It's Your City, It's Our Job."
Series VIII: Audio Cassettes--Ken Nash Collection, 1986-1999, contains audio cassettes collected by DC 37's Ken Nash, who was a producer and host of the radio show, "Building Bridges: Your Community & Labor Report." This series is organized into six subseries; the bulk are cassettes of DC 37's radio show "It's Your City, It's Our Job."
Series IX: Audio Reels--Other, 1965, includes 40 audio reels that appear to be radio spots. Some are in Spanish. These audio reels came to Tamiment with the DC 37 Photographs collection.
NOTE: This collection is housed offsite and advance notice is required for use.
Arrangement
Files arranged alphabetically by topic within each series.
The files are grouped into nine series:
Series I: Constitution and Minutes, 1955-2004.
Series II: Executive Office Records, 1951-1999.
Series III: Legal Department Records,1956-1986.
Series IV: Communications Department Records, 1963-2004.
Series V: General Files, 1944-2000.
Series VI: Restricted Materials, 1967-1997.
Series VII: Audio Reels--Ken Nash Collection, 1977-1990.
Series VIII: Audio Cassettes--Ken Nash Collection, 1986-1999.
Series IX: Audio Reels--Other.
Related Material at the Tamiment Library/Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
AFSCME, DC 37 Photographs (Photos 247)
AFSCME, DC 37, Local 1306 Records (WAG 290)
AFSCME, DC 37, Local 1930 Records (WAG 40)
AFSCME, DC 37, Local 1930: Ray Markey Files (WAG 286)
AFSCME, DC 37, Local 420 Records (WAG 215)
Bernard and Jewel Bellush Papers (WAG 30)
Civil Service Technical Guild Records (WAG 24)
Social Service Employees Union Records (WAG 3)
AFSCME.; Gotbaum, Victor; Handman, Edward, 1924-; Hill, Stanley, 1936-; New York (N.Y.). Board of Education.; New York City Health and Hospitals Corporation.; Roberts, Lillian; Schleicher, Bill; Taibi, Calogero; Wurf, Jerry, 1919-; African Americans and labor unions.; Audiocassettes.; Audiotapes.; Civil service |z New York (State) |z New York.; Clippings (information artifacts).; Collective bargaining |x Government employees |z New York (State) |z New York; Correspondence.; Finance, Public |z New York (State) |z New York.; Fliers (printed matter); Government employee unions |z New York (State) |z New York.; Hospitals |x Employees |x Labor unions |z United States.; Labor unions |x Corrupt practices.; Labor unions |x Political activity |z United States.; Labor unions |x Public relations |z United States.; Minutes.; Municipal officials and employees |x Labor unions |z New York (State) |z New York.; New York (N.Y.); New York (N.Y.) |x Economic conditions.; New York (N.Y.) |x Officials and employees.; New York (N.Y.) |x Politics and government |y 1951-; Newsletters.; Nurses' aides.; Pay equity.; White collar workers |x Labor unions |z New York (State) |z New York.
- Series I: Constitution and Minutes, 1955-2004.
  - Constitution, undated, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Minutes: Delegates, undated, 1955-1956 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Minutes: Delegates, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Minutes: Delegates, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Minutes: Delegates, 1959-1960 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Minutes: Delegates, 1960-1968 (Film R-7424)
  - Minutes: Delegates, 1970-1973 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Minutes: Delegates, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Minutes: Delegates, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Minutes: Delegates, 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Minutes: Delegates, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Minutes: Delegates, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Minutes: Delegates, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Minutes: Delegates, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Minutes: Delegates, 2001-2002 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Minutes: Delegates, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Minutes: Delegates, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Minutes: Executive Board, 1956-1957 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Minutes: Executive Board, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Minutes: Executive Board, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Minutes: Executive Board, 1959-1968 (Film R-7424)
  - Minutes: Executive Board, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Minutes: Executive Board, 1961-1962 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Minutes: Executive Board, 1970-1972 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Minutes: Executive Board, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Minutes: Executive Board, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Minutes: Executive Board, 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Minutes: Executive Board, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Minutes: Executive Board, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Minutes: Executive Board, 1990-Jun 1991 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Minutes: Executive Board, Jul 1991-Dec 1991 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Minutes: Executive Board, 1996, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Minutes: Executive Board, 2001-2003 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Minutes: Executive Board, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Minutes: Finance Committee, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Minutes: Finance Committee, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Minutes: Finance Committee, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Minutes: Finance Committee, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Minutes: Finance Committee, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Minutes: Finance Committee, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Minutes: Finance Committee, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Minutes: Finance Committee, Jan 1978-Jun 1978 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Minutes: Finance Committee, Jul 1978-Dec 1978 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Minutes: Finance Committee, Jan 1979-Jun 1979 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Minutes: Finance Committee, Jul 1979-Dec 1979 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Minutes: Finance Committee, Jan 1991-Jun 1991 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Minutes: Finance Committee, Jul 1991-Dec 1991 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Minutes: Trustees, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Series II: Executive Office Records, 1951-1999.
  - Subseries II:A: Stanley Hill Executive Director Records, 1987-1999.
    - Address Book, undated (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Agenda for Children Tomorrow, 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - American Committee on Africa (ACOA): Correspondence, 1991, 1996-Jun 1997 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - ACOA: Correspondence, Jul 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - ACOA: Press Releases and Printed Material, 1996-1998 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO), 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees (AFSCME) (Albany, NY), 1991, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - AFSCME (Washington, D.C.), 1990-1991, 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - AFSCME (Washington, D.C.) I, 1996-1998 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - AFSCME (Washington, D.C.) II, 1996-1998 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - AFSCME: Employee's Pension Plan, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - AFSCME: Lobby Day, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - AFSCME: Press Releases and Printed Material, 1991, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - AFSCME International Conventions, 1996, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - AFSCME PEOPLE Program, 1996-1998 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - AFSCME Task Force for the Future I, 1996-1998 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - AFSCME Task Force for the Future II, 1996-1998 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - AFSCME, Council 13, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - AFSCME, Council 20, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - AFSCME, Council 82 (Security and Law Enforcement Employees), 1990 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - AFSCME, District Council 1707, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Asian Pacific American Labor Alliance, 1996-1998 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Association for a Better New York, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Association for Union Democracy, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Bellevue Hospital Center, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Bellevue Hospital Community Board, 1991, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Benefits Trust Fund, 1990-1991, 1996-1997 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Black History Month, 1991, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Black History Month, 1998-1999 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Black Leadership Commission on AIDS, 1996-1998 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Blue Collar Division, 1996-1998 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Blue Collar Division: Contract Issues, 1994, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Blue Collar Division: Reports, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Blue Collar Division: Schedules, 1996-1997 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Bridge and Tunnel Officers Benevolent Association v. Triborough Bridge and Tunnel Authority (Lukas et al. v. Ascher et al.), 1996 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Campaign to Save our Public Hospitals, 1996-1997 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Campaign to Save our Public Hospitals (Oversize), 1996-1997 (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - Center on AIDS, Drugs and Community Health, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Central Park Conservancy, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Child Care Services, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Citizenship Program, 1996-1998 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - City Project (Alter Budget), 1998 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - City University of New York (CUNY), 1991, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - CUNY: Collective Bargaining, 1996-1998 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Citywide Administrative Services, 1996-1998 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Citywide Employee Orientation Manual, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Clerical Division, 1991, 1996-1997 (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - Clerical Division: Job Center Reports, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - Clippings, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - Coalition of Black Trade Unionists (CBTU), New York Chapter, 1991, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - CBTU Convention (Minneapolis), 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - Coalition on Economic Priorities, 1990-1991 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Collective Bargaining: General, 1990, 1995-1997 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Commission on the Public's Health System, 1997-1998 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Committee for Real Change in DC 37 (Reform Coalition), 1998 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Coney Island Hospital, 1991, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Contract Negotiations and Settlement: Citywide DC 37 and IBT Local 237, 1990-1991 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Cornell University: Trade Union Women's Studies Program, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence: General, 1990-Mar 1991 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence: General, Apr 1991-Sep 1991 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence: General, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence: General, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence: Internal, 1990-1991, 1995-1999 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Council for Unity, 1996-1998 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Democratic National Committee, 1990-1991, 1995-1998 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Domestic Partners/COBRA Settlement, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Education Department, 1990-1991 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Education Fund, 1990-1991, 1996-1998 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Empire BlueCross BlueShield, 1996-1998 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Empire BlueCross BlueShield: Annual Reports, 1997-1998 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Employee Recognition/Staff Holiday Party, 1996-1998 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Ethical Practices Code, undated (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Excelsior Capital Corporation: Policy Advisory Committee, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Executive Board: Correspondence, 1990-1992 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Financial Reports, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Financial Statements and Budgets, 1997-1998 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Fire Department of New York, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Greater New York Hospital Association, 1997-1998 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Harlem Hospital, 1997-1998 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Health and Security Department, 1991, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Health and Security Plan, 1990-1991 1998 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Health Care Reform, 1991, 1994-1998 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Health Systems Agency of New York City I, 1990, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Health Systems Agency of New York City II, 1990, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - HIP Foundation, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - HIP Health Plans, 1991, 1996-1997 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - HIP Health Plans, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - HIV/AIDS, 1990, 1996-1997 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Hill, Stanley: Newspaper Coverage, 1996, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Hill, Stanley et al v. Rudolph Giuliani (Hospital Closures), 1996 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Hospital Association of New York State: Regulatory Reform, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Hospital Support Sunday, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Hospitals Division: Correspondence, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Hospitals Division: Reports I, 1996-1997 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Hospitals Division: Reports II, 1996-1997 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Intermodal Surface Transportation Efficiency Act of 1991, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Invitations, 1990-1991 1998 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Kings County Hospital, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Jobs with Justice, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Labor Advisory Board, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Labor Coalition, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Legal Department: Correspondence, 1990, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Legal Department: Reports, 1996-1997 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Legislative Issues (Federal), 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Lesbian and Gay Issues Committee, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Local 154 (Amalgamated Professional Employees), 1991 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Local 299, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Local 371 (Social Service Employees Union, SSEU), 1991, 1997-1999 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Local 372 (Board of Education) I, 1990-1992, 1994-1998 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Local 372 (Board of Education) II, 1990-1992, 1994-1998 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Local 372 (Board of Education) III, 1990-1992, 1994-1998 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Local 372 (Board of Education): Administratorship, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Local 372 (Board of Education): Grievances, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Local 374 (Quasi-Public Employees), 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Local 375 (Civil Service Technical Guild, CSTG), 1991, 1996-1998 (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Local 376 (Construction Laborers, Highway Repairers, and Watershed Maintainers), 1998 (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Local 376 (Construction Laborers, Highway Repairers, and Watershed Maintainers): Grievances, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Local 384 (CUNY and Educational Opportunity Centers) I, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Local 384 (CUNY and Educational Opportunity Centers) II, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Local 420 (Municipal Hospital Employees Union), 1990-1991, 1996-1998 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Local 420 (Municipal Hospital Employees Union): Grievances, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Local 436 (United Federation of Nurses and Epidemiologists), 1998 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Local 768 (Health Services Employees), 1991, 1997-1998 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Local 924 (Laborers), 1991, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Local 957 (Housing Authority Clericals), 1998 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Local 983 (Motor Vehicle Operators), 1990, 1997-1998 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Local 983 (Motor Vehicle Operators): Grievances, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Local 983 (Motor Vehicle Operators): High Pressure Plant Tenders, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Local 1070 (Court, County, and Department of Probation Employees), 1991, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Local 1189 (Psychologists), 1998 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Local 1219 (Real Estate Employees), 1990, 1997-1998 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Local 1306 (American Museum of Natural History), 1998 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Local 1321 (Queens Library Guild), 1996, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Local 1359 (Rent Regulation Services Employees), 1997-1998 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Local 1407 (Accountants, Statisticians and Actuaries), 1991, 1997-1998 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Local 1457 (Juvenile Center), 1998 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Local 1482 (Brooklyn Library Guild), 1998 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Local 1501 (New York Zoological Society), 1996 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Local 1502 (Brooklyn Museum), 1998 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Local 1503 (Metropolitan Museum of Art), 1995, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Local 1505 (Attendants, Park Service Workers, City Park Workers and Debris Removers), 1991, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Local 1508 (Uniformed Park Supervisors), 1990 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Local 1508 (Uniformed Park Supervisors): Grievances, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Local 1549 (Clerical-Administrative Employees), 1997-1998 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Local 1549 (Clerical-Administrative Employees): New York City Police Department Group Grievance, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Local 1559 (American Museum of Natural History), 1996 (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Local 1655 (Metropolitan Transit Authority, MTA Clerical-Administrative Employees), 1991 (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - Local 1665 (Museum of the City of New York), 1995, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - Local 1757 (Assessors, Appraisers and Mortgage Analysts), 1991, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Local 1759 (Consumer Affairs Inspectors), 1998 (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - Local 1930 (New York Public Library Guild), 1990-1991 1998 (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - Local 1931 (Triborough Bridge and Tunnel Association, TBTA Maintenance Employees), 1990-1991 1998 (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - Local 2021 (Off-Track Betting Corporation), 1991, 1998-1999 (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - Local 2054 (College Assistants), 1991, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - Local 1507 (Uniformed EMTs and Paramedics), 1991, 1997-1998 (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - Local 2627 (Electronic Data Processing Personnel), 1990-1991, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - Local 3621 (Uniformed EMS Officers), 1991, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - Locals: Lists, 1995-1998 (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - Medicaid, 1996-1998 (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - Membership and Agency Shop Fee Payer Tally (by Local and Title), 1991 (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - Metropolitan Hospital, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 44)
    - Metropolitan Martin Luther Kind Center for Nonviolence, 1997-1998 (Box 6, Folder 45)
    - Metropolitan Transit Authority (MTA), 1990, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 46)
    - MTA, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 47)
    - Municipal Employees' Legal Services Plan (MELS), 1990-1991, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 48)
    - Municipal Labor Committee (MLC), 1990-1991, 1996-1998 (Box 6, Folder 49)
    - MLC: Minutes, 1997-1998 (Box 6, Folder 50)
    - National Housing Conference, 1997-1998 (Box 6, Folder 51)
    - National Union of Hospital and Health Care Employees, Local 1199, 1997-1998 (Box 6, Folder 52)
    - Neponsit Health Center, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 53)
    - New York Central Labor Council (NYCLC): Correspondence, 1990-1991, 1996-Apr-97 (Box 6, Folder 54)
    - NYCLC: Correspondence, May 1997-Dec 1997 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - NYCLC: Correspondence, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - NYCLC: Labor News Briefs, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - NYCLC: Press Releases and Printed Material, 1991, 1994, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - NYCLC: Public Hearing Schedule, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - New York City Board of Education, 1987, 1990-1991, 1995-1998 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - New York City Board of Education: Allocation Memorandum, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - New York City Budget, 1996-1998 (Box 7, Folder 8)